Contact

cmatthe2@ycp.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/claramatthews-bsn-rn-csfa-8050a78b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Nursing

Clara Matthews, BSN, RN, CSFA

Owner of Precise Nursing & Surgical Services, LLC York, Pennsylvania

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Inpatient Care, Clinical Research, and Operating Room. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Nursingfrom York College of Pennsylvania.

Experience

Travel Nurse RN, Operating Room Travel Nurse June 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month) Georgia

WellSpan Health
11 years 4 months
Registered Nurse, Operating Room
June 2012 - June 2015 (3 years 1 month)

Licensed Practical Nurse March 2004 - June 2012 (8 years 4 months)

Crispus Attucks Association of York, Pennsylvania School Nurse, RN 2013 - 2015 (2 years)

Education

York College of Pennsylvania BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse